Department of Philosophy fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Departmental meeting and committee files, 1964 - 1978; F-15-4; 39 cm of textual records 18 sound recordings: 31 audio cassettes
  - Departmental Tenure Committee files, 1964 - 1978; F-15-4-3; 23 cm of textual records
    - Tenure committee, 1972 - 1973; F-15-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure committee, 1974 - 1977; F-15-4-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure - B, 1973; F-15-4-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure - C, 1974 - 1978; F-15-4-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure - D, 1972 - 1975; F-15-4-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure - F, 1971 - 1973; F-15-4-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure - F, 1974; F-15-4-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure - F, 1974 - 1975; F-15-4-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - G, 1964 - 1968; F-15-4-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - H, 1972 - 1973; F-15-4-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - J, 1974 - 1975; F-15-4-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - K, 1972; F-15-4-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - S, 1967 - 1973; F-15-4-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - T, 1970 - 1972; F-15-4-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - T, 1972 - 1973; F-15-4-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - W, 1971 - 1972; F-15-4-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
    - Tenure - Z, 1973 - 1976; F-15-4-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee files, 1973 - 1978; F-15-4-4; 1 cm of textual records
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973 - 1978; F-15-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
- Faculty and university committee files, 1975 - 1977; F-15-5; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to departmental representation on the Dean's Advisory Committee and the University Review Committee. Records includes memoranda and minutes.
  - Dean's advisory committee, 1975 - 1977; F-15-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-13)
  - University Review Committee, 1977; F-15-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
- Course files, 1965 - 1986; F-15-6; 65 cm of textual records
  Series consists of files of undergraduate course outlines and examinations, as well as course offerings booklets.
  - Course offerings, 1967 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
    Open
  - Course offerings booklets, 1973 - 1974; F-15-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Graduate course offerings, 1970 - 1974; F-15-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Course evaluations, F-15-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Logic notes, 1970; F-15-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 100, 1966 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 101, 1965; F-15-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 102, 1967 - 1970; F-15-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 102, 1971 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 103, 1965 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 200, 1966 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 202, 1966 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 204, 1966 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 15-14)
  - Philosophy 205, 1966 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 206, 1968 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 207, 1969 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 208, 1970 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 209, 1970 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 400, 1966 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 401, 1969 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 404, 1969 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 405, 1968 - 1970; F-15-6-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 406, 1968 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 407, 1970 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 411, 1967 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 413, 1970 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 420, 1968 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 430, 1968 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 431, 1967 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 432, 1969 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 433, 1966 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 434, 1967 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 437, 1969 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 440, 1968 - 1970; F-15-6-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 442, 1970; F-15-6-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 800, 1968 - 1969; F-15-6-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 810, 1971; F-15-6-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 820, 1969; F-15-6-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 830, 1970 - 1972; F-15-6-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 840, 1970 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 870, 1969 - 1970; F-15-6-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Philosophy 871, 1970; F-15-6-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 15-15)
  - Course offerings, 1970 - 1977; F-15-6-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
  - Course structure, 1970 - 1971; F-15-6-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
  - Philosophy 001, 1973 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 100, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 110, 1972; F-15-6-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 110, 1973; F-15-6-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 110, 1974; F-15-6-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 110, 1978 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 120, 1973 - 1985; F-15-6-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 15-19)
  - Philosophy 130, 1975 - 1981; F-15-6-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 140, 1980 - 1981; F-15-6-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 150, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 151, 1976 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 203, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 210, 1972 - 1986; F-15-6-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 214, 1980 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 220, 1973 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 231, 1972 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 240, 1973 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 241, 1972 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 242, 1973 - 1980; F-15-6-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 243, 1979 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 244, 1984; F-15-6-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 250, 1973 - 1974; F-15-6-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 280, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 300, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 15-20)
  - Philosophy 301, 1980 - 1981; F-15-6-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 310, 1967 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 314, 1976 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 320, 1980 - 1981; F-15-6-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 321, 1980 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 325, 1983 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 331, 1973 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 340, 1973 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 341, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 343, 1973 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 344, 1972 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 350, 1973 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 353, 1976 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 354, 1972 - 1980; F-15-6-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 355, 1973 - 1979; F-15-6-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 360, 1973 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 402, 1973 - 1974; F-15-6-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 410, 1975; F-15-6-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 414, 1975 - 1977; F-15-6-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 421, 1973 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 435, 1973 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 444, 1974 - 1982; F-15-6-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 445, 1975 - 1980; F-15-6-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 451, 1973 - 1977; F-15-6-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 452, 1980 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 453, 1972 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 455, 1972 - 1984; F-15-6-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 467, 1973 - 1983; F-15-6-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
  - Philosophy 468, 1975 - 1981; F-15-6-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 15-21)
- Publications, 1968 - 1989; F-15-7; 4 cm of textual records
  Series consists of departmental publications, including course offerings booklets.
  - Publications, 1968 - 1988; F-15-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-16)
  - Publications, 1989; F-15-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-16)
- Association files, 1968; F-15-8; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Canadian Association of University Teachers. It includes correspondence and memoranda.
  - Canadian Association of University Teachers, 1968; F-15-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-16)
- Conference files, 1973 - 1980; F-15-9; 6 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the Articulation Committee and conferences hosted by the Department or attended by faculty members. It includes booklets, correspondence, memoranda, minutes, and reports.
  - Articulation committee, 1973 - 1975; F-15-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-16)
  - SFU - UVic conference, 1976 - 1980; F-15-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-16)
  - Conferences, 1979 - 1980; F-15-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-16)